{
    "id": "02a918bbd9b84aaeba7f4d7d70528905",
    "title": "Sentence Agreement Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Economics ............................. his favourite subject.",
            "description": "Some nouns look plural with -s but they take a singular verb. Examples are: physics, mathematics, economics, mumps, measles, diabetes, rabies, news, politics, ethics, athletics, gymnastics, aerobics.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Measles ............................. highly contagious.",
            "description": "Some nouns look plural with -s but they take a singular verb. Examples are: physics, mathematics, economics, mumps, measles, diabetes, rabies, news, politics, ethics, athletics, gymnastics, aerobics.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Diabetes ............................ in my family.",
            "description": "Some nouns look plural with -s but they take a singular verb. Examples are: physics, mathematics, economics, mumps, measles, diabetes, rabies, news, politics, ethics, athletics, gymnastics, aerobics.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "run",
                "runs",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Rabies .............................. incurable.",
            "description": "Some nouns look plural with -s but they take a singular verb. Examples are: physics, mathematics, economics, mumps, measles, diabetes, rabies, news, politics, ethics, athletics, gymnastics, aerobics.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Aerobics ............................ good for health.",
            "description": "Some nouns look plural with -s but they take a singular verb. Examples are: physics, mathematics, economics, mumps, measles, diabetes, rabies, news, politics, ethics, athletics, gymnastics, aerobics.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "No news .............................. good news.",
            "description": "Some nouns look plural with -s but they take a singular verb. Examples are: physics, mathematics, economics, mumps, measles, diabetes, rabies, news, politics, ethics, athletics, gymnastics, aerobics.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Gymnastics ........................... her hobby at school.",
            "description": "Some nouns look plural with -s but they take a singular verb. Examples are: physics, mathematics, economics, mumps, measles, diabetes, rabies, news, politics, ethics, athletics, gymnastics, aerobics.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "What .............................. pliers used for?",
            "description": "Use a plural verb with jeans, trousers, pants, scissors, pliers etc. ",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "My family ............................. lived in this house for twenty years.",
            "description": "Family can be followed by either a singular or a plural verb. ",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The police ................................. searching for a bald guy in his forties.",
            "description": "Use a plural verb with police.",
            "answers": [
                "are",
                "is",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Where ......................... my jeans?",
            "description": "Use a plural verb with jeans, trousers, pants, scissors, pliers etc. ",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The staff .............................. not happy with the decision of the management.",
            "description": "Staff is usually followed by a plural verb. ",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}